欢迎加入OCR小组 qq群906722936 字幕优先发布于群内 字幕广告招租 商业合作Q:1585235535
索恩 我想跟你私下谈谈
I need to speak with you privately.
-我们去兜兜风吧  -好的长官
Let's take a ride. Yes, sir.
他把一切都告诉我了 给了我完整简报
He told me everything, gave me the full briefing.
梯队简报
The Echelon Briefing?
公民共和军会把世界带回来
Jadis: The CRM will bring the world back.
告诉我你不会去追杀他们
Tell me you won't come after them.
不 因为我们要去找他们
No. Because we are coming for them.
我们会拿到档案
We're gonna get the dossier.
他会得到梯队简报
He's gonna get the Echelon Briefing
找出他们所做的
and find out everything that they do
而这个城市却不知道的一切
that the city doesn't know about
我们会帮助城市阻止他们
We're gonna help the city stop them.
我都记得
Rick: I remember it all.
那是什么样子
What it was like.
我们曾经是谁 现在是谁
Who we were. Who we are now.
我叫米琼恩
Michonne: My name is Michonne.
我失去了一个人
I lost someone.
很多年前就失去了
Years ago.
他们二人都具有成为公民共和军所需的特质
Okafor: Both of them have something I believe the CRM
有着发展成为其所需形态的潜力
needs to become what it needs to be.
人是一种资源
Jadis: People are a resource.
我知道如何建造
Nat: I know how to build things,
如何摧毁
and I know how to burn things,
但末世之中需要的不仅仅是这些
but it takes more than that at the end of the world.
你试图逃跑过四次
Beale: You tried to escape four times.
你为什么会在这里
Why are you here?
外面有你爱的人
Thorne: There's someone you love out there.
你还爱我吗
Michonne: Do you still love me?
一直都爱
Rick: Always.
听起来很简单对不对
Michonne: It sounds simple, right?
我们分头进去 你去拿简报
We each go in. You get the briefing,
我去拿她留下的档案
I get the dossier she left behind.
我们让城市知晓我们已知的一切 然后回家
We bring what we know to the city, then go home.
一起回家
Together.
从来都不会那么简单
It's never that simple.
我是瑞克·格莱姆斯军士长
Rick: I'm Sergeant Major Rick Grimes.
你可能以为我死了
You probably think I'm dead.
他说我不必害怕
He said I didn't need to be scared,
那不过是“摧毁”
that it was just"the burning. "
你真的在这里
You're really here.
是啊
Yeah.
你向他们汇报了情况 现在告诉我是怎么回事
You gave them the debrief. Now tell me what happened.
当时出现气流
Well, there was turbulence.
我们降低了飞行高度想冲出来
We - We went low to get out of it.
-被闪电击中  -嗯
We were struck by lightning. Yeah.
掉到水上滑行 贝休恩把我推出来
We were going down over water, and Bethune shoved me out.
她救了我的命
She saved my life.
却没能活下来 只救下了我
Not hers, mine.
谢谢你吸收她进来
So thank you for bringing her in.
不是 是你招募她的
No, you brought her in.
我们何不直接说是奥卡福呢
Why don't we just say it was Okafor?
我们只是在继续发扬他的事业
That we were just keeping his thing going.
我以前觉得放弃
I used to think that giving up
就是缺乏个性
meant a lack of character
意志薄弱
and a- - a weak will.
但你和我 我们放弃了那么多才走到这步
But you and I, we gave up so much to be here.
现在我意识到放弃可以是力量的象征
And now I realize that giving up can be a sign of strength.
对比自己更重要的事情的承诺
A commitment to something bigger than oneself.
放弃让我明白了我们在这里真正的目的
Giving up made me understand what we're really doing here.
希望你也能明白
Hopefully, you will understand, too.
我希望可以
Iwant to.
很高兴你活下来了 瑞克
I'm glad you made it, Rick.
大家很需要你
You are needed.
这取决于我们 而不是
It is up to us, but not like
像奥卡福说的那样
Okafor said.
奥卡福 他
Okafor, he
身在曹营心在汉 没有全身心投入进来
He was never really here, not in the way he should have been.
所以他才死了
That's why he died.
但你活下来了 我活下来了
But you lived. I lived.
我们注定要成为其中一员
We are meant to be a part of this.
是时候忘掉他的废话了
It's time to let go of his bullshit.
给我指明另一条路
Well, show me the other way.
威胁解除
Threat neutralized.
我去周围搜查一下
I'm gonna take a sweep of the perimeter.
他想跟你谈谈
He wants to talk to you.
瑞克
Rick.
就是这里
This is it.
我从没必要做这事
I never had to do this.
我从没必要为成为公民而杀掉六个行尸 因为我
I never had to do my six for citizenship because I- -
我从来没成为过一个真正的公民
I never really became a citizen.
世界终结和开始
The end of the world and the beginning of the world.
死的会是我们 瑞克
And we're the dead ones, Rick.
我们跟他们有点类似
We're kind of like them.
但他们杀戮只是为了谋求食物或出于强迫
But they only kill for food or out of compulsion.
-对不对  -是的
Isn't that right? It is.
我们的科学家还是没有解决方案
Our scientists haven't figured it out.
也许以后都不会有
Maybe they never will.
但我们 另一种死去的人
But us, the other kind of dead ones,
我们有这个
we have this.
杀戮之剑即是赋予生命之剑
The sword that kills is the sword that gives life.
这就是我们 我们就是这把剑
And that's us. We're the sword.
行动前一天 我让助理和副官们退下了
I have my aides and lieutenants leave me in solitude
独留我一个人
the day before an operation.
我不喜欢被分心
I don't like distractions.
我独自决定前进的道路
I alone decided the path ahead,
独自感受它的重量
and I alone want to feel the weight of it.
从无例外
I never interrupt that time.
但你来了
But you are here.
经历这一切之后
After everything.
令我自愧不如
And I am humbled by that.
所以 我会同你共度些时光
So, I'll share some time with you,
也许甚至会让你承担部分重量
maybe even ask you to carry some of that weight.
斯托克斯警官 你在里面吗
Woman: Officer Stokes? Are you in there?
把枪放桌子上
Put your gun on the table.
那个带刀片的假肢
That prosthetic with the blade.
放我前面 离你远点
In front of me. Away from you.
我希望你能反思下自己的人生
I want you to reflect on your life.
此刻之前和之后的所有的人生经历
On all your lives before and after.
所有之前和之后的事情
AlI the before and afters.
此刻之前你所做的一切
AlI the things you did before this moment.
因为
Because.
下一刻之后
after this next moment,
一切都会改变
everything will change.
为了让其他人活下来
What was the worst thing you did
你做过的最糟糕的事是什么
to make sure someone else survived?
我用牙齿杀过人
I killed someone with my teeth.
就像他们一样
Like they do.
很抱歉你不得不那么做
I'm sorry you had to do that.
倒是不必
Oh, you don't have to be.
可还是很不爽 对不对
Still, it's a damn thing, isn't it?
是的 是的 长官
Yes. Yes, it is, sir.
你做出了一些非同寻常的选择 格莱姆斯
You've made some extraordinary choices, Grimes.
我已经做过这个简报
I've given this briefing,
梯队简报 2533次
the Echelon Briefing, 2, 533 times.
只有我和精英士兵
Just me and the elite soldier in question.
而任何一位精英士兵
And the soldier in question
都从未像你这样
has never been someone like you.
从没有过
Never.
这是第一步
This is the first.
是下一步的开始
It's the start of what's next.
今天来做再合适不过了
And that couldn't be more appropriate for today.
完全为了
A day completely about
明天的一天
tomorrow.
我好想你
I missed you so much.
言语都表达不出我的思念
Words can't even say it right.
你不用说
You don't have to.
我知道的
I know.
我们是不是疯了
Are we crazy?
肯定是
Certifiable.
我在匹兹堡长大
I grew up in Pittsburgh.
我酒鬼父亲打断了我下巴的那天
The same day my alcoholic father broke my jaw,
我离家出走 在海外退伍军人协会找了份工
I left home and landed a job at a VFW hall.
吧台助理
Barback.
那年我15岁
I was 15.
那些海外退伍军人协会的男人女人们
And those men and women at the VFW,
成了我真正的父母
they became my real parents.
他们造就了我
They were who formed me.
我18岁那年 参军入伍
So when I was 18, I signed up to fight.
去了越南
I went to Vietnam.
但那之后还走了不短的一段旅程
But there was a whole journey beyond that.
本宁堡 军官训练
Fort Benning, officer training.
后来那段旅程把我带回了宾夕法尼亚
Then the journey led me back to Pennsylvania,
回到了国民警卫队 进到了指挥部
to its National Guard, and through its command,
感谢上帝
thank God.
我离开了
I went away.
不得不走
I had to.
我本可以让世界把我带走
I could've let the world take me away.
但我回来了
But I came back
像你一样
like you.
收到 长官
Woman: Copy that, sir.
你说你一开始就看到了
You said you saw what the federal forces
联邦军队做了什么
did at the beginning.
是的
I did.
他们轰炸了城市
They bombed the cities.
奥卡福说他们称之为“清除病媒”
Okafor said that they called it clearing disease vectors. "
-病媒 对  -他们的词
"Vectors, "yeah. Their word.
我决定自己来对付他们
I made the decision to take them on ourselves.
第二次内战发生在宾夕法尼亚州
Second Civil War fought on good Pennsylvania ground.
有两条战线 匹兹堡和费城
There were two fronts Pittsburgh and Philadelphia.
我们输了
And we were losing.
我们无法维持两个战区作战
We couldn't sustain two theaters of battle.
在我的家乡 我们有地形和战术的优势
In my hometown, we had an opportunity of terrain,
还有大量行尸
tactics, and a massive incoming dead mass
而联邦军队并不知道
that the federal forces were unaware of.
所以 我在夜幕的掩护下撤离了我们的部队
So, uh, I evacuated our forces under the cover of night
让大量行尸压制他们的部队
and let the dead overwhelm their troops.
还有整个城市
And that whole city.
我牺牲匹兹堡拯救了费城
I saved Philadelphia by sacrificing Pittsburgh.
我的敌人们 朋友们
My enemies, my friends
还有我的家
my home.
虽然算不上是用自己的犬牙去咬人
It's not exactly tearing into a person with your canines,
但也不能说什么都不是 对吗
but it's not nothing. Isn't that right?
的确不能说什么都不是 长官
No, it's not nothing, sir.
我爸教过我 无论如何
My dad taught me, for better or worse
有时候只有推倒一切才能重来
...sometimes things have to burn to bring things back.
是这么回事
It was that.
杀戮之剑即是赋予生命之剑
The sword that kills is the sword that gives life.
我扼杀了自己的过去和整个城市
I killed my past and a whole city
这样另一个城市才能生存
so another could live.
让我告诉你第一个秘密 格莱姆斯
Let me tell you the first secret, Grimes.
这是我和每个前线队员
The first one that I share with each Frontliner
分享的第一件事
I've briefed.
经过所有的战斗和杀戮 所有的计划和牺牲
The most likely outcome after all the fighting and killing,
最有可能的结果是 我们输了
all the plans and sacrifices, we lose.
最有可能的结果是我们都会死
Most likely outcome is that we're all gonna die.
能力评估概述马上就要开始了
Man: The CEP overview will begin imminently.
这是一次强制参加的简报
This is a mandatory briefing.
请签到参加
Please sign for review.
大家注意了 眼睛看前面
Man#2: Heads up, everyone. Eyes front.
N1W行动中最敏感的一个方面
Man#3: One of the most sensitive aspects
是儿童撤离协议
to Operation N1W is the Child Evacuation Protocol.
这么说 我们就是这样出生的
So, we were born this way.
我想是的
I guess so.
我们在那里发现了数百万的行尸
We've discovered million- strong dead masses out there.
我们的模型显示 神经非坏死的人类生命
Our modeling shows that non- necrotic human life
也就是活人 在这个星球上还剩下14年可活
people ...now have 14 or so years left on this planet.
可能会更快
Could be quicker.
而且这不仅是因为行尸
And it isn't just the delts.
而是饥饿 人口和粮食产量之间的
It's starvation the tenuous balance
脆弱平衡
between population and yield.
疾病 有十亿培养皿
Disease, with a billion petri dishes
在太阳的暴晒下四处溜达
out there stumbling and cooking in the sun,
等着把不知道什么鬼东西传染给我们
waiting to transmit God knows what to us
然后变成跟他们一样的东西
while it transforms into God knows what.
最后 最有可能的结果是
And in the end, the most likely outcome
这块岩石会堆满尸体
is that this rock will be cluttered with corpses
最终腐烂成树木的食物
to eventually rot into food for the trees.
这一切都会变成一个奇怪的临时博物馆
And it all becomes a strange temporary museum
等到一个更奇怪的物种征服了它
to an even stranger species that conquered it
并记录了它曾存在的一瞬间
and marked it for a blink of its existence.
所以我们才会做这些
This is why we do what we do.
我们到底在做什么 长官
What do you do, sir?
我们试图战胜困难 格莱姆斯
We're trying to beat the odds, Grimes.
通过公民共和军一线战士以假身份
Man#3: Through CRM Frontliner embeds living in Portland
在波特兰生活 多年来
under false identities, we have, over years,
我们让特工潜入波特兰的学校系统
had operatives enmeshed in the Portland school system
帮助疏散选定的孩子
to facilitate an evacuation of selected children.
公民共和军破坏社区是为了资源
The CRM destroys communities for resources,
为了战略优势
for strategic superiority,
首先是为了确保城市的保密性和安全性
and to ensure the city's secrecy and security above all.
一旦在波特兰的行动开始
Once the operation on Portland begins,
孩子们将被空运离开三所学校
children will be airlifted away from three school sites.
这将导致城市中10%的儿童撤离
It will result in an evacuation of possibly 10%of the children
然后该地区会被毒气袭击
in the city before the area is gassed
人口被清除
and its population is liquidated.
我们在整个非洲大陆
We have embeds - spies- -
和世界各地的特定社区都安插了间谍
in selected communities throughout the continent
监视他们 潜在的进行破坏
and the world to monitor them, to pσtentially sabotage them,
影响他们的政治和做事方法
to influence their politics and approaches.
直到最近 我们还为公民共和军运营的实验室
Up until recently, we supplied test subjects
提供了科学实验的测试对象
for scientiific experiments to CRM- run labs.
奥马哈并没有消亡
Omaha didn't just die.
我们摧毁了它 连同它的校园殖民地
We destroyed it, along with its Campus Colony.
18小时后 我们将采取最后行动
And in 18 hours, we will take our final action
让我们成为这片大陆上 也许是世界上
to leave us as the supreme force on this continent,
最强大的力量
maybe the world.
我们会摧毁波特兰
We will destroy Portland.
我们告诉共和国的人民 公民共和军是做什么的
We tell the Civic Republic what the CRM does.
比如轰炸 还有他们做的其他事情
Like the bombing, whatever else they do.
如果我们不说 谁还会说呢
If we don't, who will?
没有人
No one.
绝不能丢下人们不管
You don't leave people behind.
这就是我们要做的事
This is the shit we do.
作为对波特兰陷落的回应
In response to the loss of Portland,
我们最后的同盟伙伴
our last alliance partner- -
我们将作为又一起悲剧 神秘和令人震惊的
which we will report as another tragic, mysterious,
事件报道 公民共和国军
shocking incident- the Civic Republic Military
将宣布对城市实施戒严令
will declare martial law on the city,
废除议会
doing away with the Council.
自由的代价太高了
Stakes are too high for freedom.
随着公民共和军控制城市和我们同盟伙伴的死亡
With the city under CRM control and our Alliance partners dead,
我们将在全国范围内进军
we will march across this country
进一步消除任何日益增长的竞争
and further eliminate any growing competition.
我们将夺取他们的资源 确保霸权
We will take their resources and ensure supremacy.
然后
And maybe
也许我们就能存活了
Maybe we get to survive.
气泡窗口会被遮拦
Man#3: Bubble windows will be in blackout.
孩子们不会看到或者听到
The children will not see or hear
这个城市里发生的一切
what is happening to the city.
至关重要的是 要保持稳定
It is critical to remain even, to be steady,
不要被孩子们将要经历的创伤
to not give in to the trauma the children will experience- -
或者是参与部队将要经历的一切所影响
or that the participating forces will experience.
我们会坐简迪斯的直升机回公民共和国
We'll get back to the Civic Republic in Jadis's helicopter.
我会带大家飞到他们意想不到的跳伞点加油
I'll fly us to jump points for the refuels they won't expect.
基地有任何变化 通过对讲机告诉我
Anything changes on base, key the walkie.
我会尽快回到你身边
I'lI get back to you when I can.
如果我还在的话
If I can be gotten back to.
你在等人呼叫吗
You expecting a call?
是索恩
That was Thorne.
她经历了这些
She went through this.
我想如果能跟她谈谈应该挺好
Thought it would be good to talk it out.
士兵们应该让孩子们把注意力放在
Man#3: Soldiers should put the children's focus
我们为他们提供的舒适物品上
on the comfort items we'll furnish them with.
不要说“一切都会好起来的”
Avoid saying, "It's going to be okay. "
只说“他们”会没事的
Just say"they" will be okay.
他们中的任何一个都可能成为
Any one of them could prove to be the difference
我们文明幸存的差异因素
in our civilization's survival.
我们将在很多方面 进行清理
We will, in many ways, scavenge...
在发生了这一切之后
After everything,
在所有的逃跑尝试之后 就在此时此地
after all the escape attempts to right here, now...
我认为下一个十年的领导者
I think that the next leader in the next decade,
可能就是你
that might be you.
这么多年 多次试图逃离之后
After trying to get away so many times,
你发现自己自由了 对我们来说你已经死了
after so many years you found yourself free, dead to us.
你可以去任何你想去的地方
You could've gone wherever it was you wanted to go.
可你却回来了
And you came back.
你会成为一个有影响力的故事
You've become a powerful story.
一个强有力的象征 一个公民共和军
A powerful symbol, one the CRM
用来讲述以赢得人心的故事
may need to tell to win the hearts of the people
因为他们将看到自己的某些自由再次被推迟
who will see some of their freedoms delayed yet again.
我牺牲过 奥卡福也牺牲过
I sacrificed. Okafor sacrificed.
我希望你也能这样
I would expect the same for you.
但你说自己已经有过牺牲
But you said it- - you already have.
听说你最亲近的人在这之中死去了 是谁
Who's the person closest to you who's died in all of this?
我儿子
My son.
我切断了那个人的喉咙去救他
He's who I saved tearing out that man's throat.
但你最后都没能救到他吗
But you couldn't save him in the end?
没有
No.
如果我告诉你
What if I told you you would never have to suffer
你再也不用承受那种损失了
that kind of loss again,
不管你要去哪里
that wherever you were running to,
不管你要去找谁
whoever you were running to...
你都能保证他们的安全 你会把他们带给我们吗
you could keep them safe, you could bring them to us?
家人 朋友 爱 不管是谁
Family, friends, a lov- - I don't give a damn.
无论我们什么时候找到他们
They will be spared from our march,
他们都不会被我们清除
whenever we would have found them.
我愿意冒这个险
I'lI take that chance.
我愿意为你冒这个险
I'm taking that chance on you.
波特兰会被摧毁
Portland will die,
而这支军队将接手公民共和国
and this force will take over the Civic Republic.
我们会从郊区开始进军
We will begin our march on the countryside.
下一个世界将会开始
The Next World will begin,
通过这个世界 我们将以某种方式生存下来
and through that, somehow, some way, we will survive.
只有推倒一切才能重来
We will burn things to bring things back.
杀戮之剑即是赋予生命之剑
The sword that kills is the sword that brings life.
以剑起誓
Swear on the sword.
我问你个问题吧 格莱姆斯
Let me ask you a question, Grimes.
我会看着你的眼睛问你这个问题
I'm just gonna ask it and look in your eyes.
以剑起誓
Swear on the sword.
别让它得逞
Don't let it take.
你为什么回来
Why did you come back? l Aah!
你走了 你死了
You were gonel You were dead!
你本可以救下你想救之人
You could've saved whoever you wanted to
然后拯救整个世界 为什么
and then saved the world. Why?
世界不会终结
The world isn't gonna end!
会的 我要确保我们不会毁灭
It is! I'm trying to make sure we don't!
该死的奥卡福
Goddamn Okafor!
我从失去过儿子
I never lost my son.
我迷失了自己
I lost myself.
他把我救了回来 我老婆把我救了回来
He brought me back. My wife brought me back.
我们是杀戮之剑
We re the sword that kills.
我们是赋予生命之剑
We're the sword that gives life.
一次生命 不可阻挡的生命
One life. One unstoppable life.
我们没死
We're not dead.
死的是你
You are.
索恩 我是格莱姆斯 完毕
Thorne? It's Grimes, over.
收到 完毕
Thorne: Copy. Over.
我收到简报了 我们晚点再谈
I got the briefing. We'll talk later.
比尔在全员出动前
Beale went to the woods to be on his own
独自一人去了树林 完毕
before the all- hands, over.
你想现在碰头吗 完毕
Do you want to meet now? Over.
比尔已经给我安排活儿了
Beale gave me something to do already.
完毕
Over.
该死
Damn it
必须去做
Got to do it.
瑞克
Rick!
我们不能回家 还不能
We can't go home. Not yet.
-不  -你知道他们会做什么吗
No. Do you know what they're gonna do?
我拿到了梯队报告 你怎么
I got the Echelon. How did you-
他们有一整个帐篷的炸弹
They have an entire tent of bombs out there.
他们已经把孩了们疏散了
They're evacuating the kids,
然后就是一整个城市的人 瑞克
then it's a whole city of people, Rick.
行动已经在进行中了
This is happening now.
我们还是可以回家的 但不是现在
We can still get home, but not yet.
我们必须阻止他们 因为我们能做到
We have to stop them, because we can stop them.
-这是你的吗  -嗯
Is this yours? Yeah.
里面有什么
What's in it?
你到底想干什么 格莱姆斯
Thorne: What are you up to, Grimes?
你怎么想出这个办法的
How'd you come up with this?
从一个叫纳特的天才那里得到的灵感
Took some inspiration from the genius known as Nat.
比尔说有一天我可以领导公民共和军
You know, Beale said I could lead the CRM one day
看来你说对了
Guess you were right.
你还真能自己做到这一切
You could do this all by yourself.
我们可以直接走
We could just go.
这是
This is
我们不得不做的
What we have to do.
如果我们任由这种事情发生
What sort of world are we making for them
我们将为他们创造一个什么样的世界
if we walk away from something like this?
你知道吗
You know
一想到错过的时间我就恼火不已
I'm mad at the time I missed.
没能看到我们的孩子成长
Not seeing our kids growing up.
我知道我们不能 但我只是
I know we can't, but I just
一想到错过的时间
I think about that time and.
我就只想立刻回家去
I just want to go back.
我们已经回家了
We are back.
而这是我们应该做的事
And this is the shit we do.
没错
Yes, it is.
格莱姆斯
Thorne: Grimes?
10分钟后召开全体会议 小队任务已发布
Man: All- hands briefing in 10. Squad assignments posted.
All- hands briefing in 10. Squad assignments posted.
最后情报
after final intelligence
ABC小队
Alpha, Bravo, Charlie
请向小队确认
...confirmed at squad level.
Confirmed at squad level.
-就这样了  -对
This is it. Yeah.
这是我们最后一次分开
This is the last we're apart.
我本该害怕
I should be scared.
站在这里 我就该害怕 但我不怕
Just standing here, I should scared, but I'm not.
因为有你
Because of you.
我忘了件事
I forgot.
有样东西要给你
I have something for you.
但如果我为她辩护 他们会觉得我情绪化 欠了人情
But if I argue for her, they'll think I'm emotional, indebted.
你要确保她能留下
You gotta make sure she stays.
我为她冒了很大的风险 为了你
I put my neck out for her. For you.
我们需要处理好
We need to take care of this.
她还没死
She's not gone.
举起手
Hands!
比尔呢
Where's Beale?
我知道你骗了我
I know you lied to me.
你做了什么
What did you do?
瑞克
Rick.
戴娜
Dana.
索恩
Thorne.
把头盔摘下来
Take off your helmets.
把包放下
Put your bag down.
你要转身 回去
You are going to turn around, you are going to go back inside,
撤销你所做的一切
and you are going to undo whatever you did.
等我找到比尔 你一定会后悔的
And when I find Beale, you're going to regret this.
继续走
Keep going!
你要纠正所有错误
You're going to fix this.
不能停手
It never died.
不会停 不能停
It won't stop. It can't stop.
这边
This wayl
把旗了拿下来盖住我们
Pull the flag down over us!
时间再长点
Just a little longer.
很快就散了
It breaks up quick.
格莱姆斯
Thorne: Grimes!
索恩来了
There's Thorne.
她有面具
She's got a mask.
我冲向她 你戴上另一个面具
I'll rush her. You get the other mask.
为什么你去
Why you?
你手里有剑 动手
You got the sword. We go?
动手
We go.
你 你毁了我们的机会
You∽You destroyed our chance!
你毁了整个世界
You destroyed the whole world!
你是他一直想接近的那个人
You were the one he was always trying to get to.
你怎么得手的
How did you get to him?
我从不放弃
I didn't give up.
我不像你那样放弃了自己
I didn't give me up like you did!
他在哪
Where is he? !
Where is he?
转身
Turn around.
你不明白
You don't understand.
在一个逝去的世界里 爱也逝去了
In a dead world, love is dead!
爱永不灭
Love doesn't die.
看着
Watch.
爱
Love.
永不
doesn't
奥卡福说的对
Okafor was right.
他说的对
He was right.
你只能希望比尔说错了
You just have to hope Beale was wrong.
快点 快点
Michonne: Come on! Come on!
N1W
Woman: ...N1W.
由于公民共和军的前线部队和部队指挥部
With the CRM's Frontliner force and the CRM Force Command
包括少将乔纳森·比尔在内
including Major General Johnathan Beale －
所有事故伤亡人员
all casualties of the incident connected
都与他们的行动和活动
with the shocking revelations
有着密切的关系
regarding all their operations and activities,
公民共和国议会一致投票
the CRC voted unanimously for emergency oversight
通过了对公民共和军剩余部队的紧急监督
over the remaining forces of the CRM.
指挥等级和作战层层保密
Man: Command hierarchies and layers of operational secrecy
表明步兵团和强化步兵部队
indicate infantry and enhanced infantry units
不知道也没有参与这些
were unaware of and did not participate in the atrocities
最高级别共和军犯下的暴行
perpetrated by these highest levels of the CRM,
因此有希望立即对此进行改革
thus presenting hope for immediate reform.
在另一项令人震惊的投票中
And in another stunning, unanimous vote by the CRC,
议会一致投票推翻了十多年来公民共和军的指导方针
overturning more than a decade of CRM guidance,
为共和国建立了自由流动机制
free movement has been established for the Republic.
市民们现在可以自由离开
Citizens are now free to leave at will,
城市也会欢迎
and the city will now welcome new citizens,
可能会到来的新市民
as they may arrive.
这是共和国开启新篇章的历史性的一天
A historic day to begin a new chapter for the Republic.
松涛 我是大东
Michonne: Shoto? It's Daito.
你们还好吗 天 你长这么大了
How are you doing? Oh, my. You're so big
你好
Hi there.
我就知道 爸
I knew it, Dad.
我就知道你还活着
I knew you were still out there.
我只是不想让你感到孤单
I just never wanted you to feel alone.
我以为我是 个人
I thought Iwas.
然后我才意识到
Then I realized
并非如此
I wasn't
你把他带回来了
You got him back
你让我这么做的
You told me to.
你就是那个勇敢的人吗
You're the brave man?
我是
I am.
他是
He is.
但也许你可以叫我爸爸
But maybe you can call me Dad.
我知道你会回米的
I knew you'd come back.
怎么知道的
How?
我深信不疑
I believed.